# **LEVIKANE**

# Chicago, IL 60639

oneleggedlevi09@gmail.com www.oneleggedlevi.com (773) 558-3112 www.github.com/levickane https://www.linkedin.com/in/levi-kane-8a94a155/

# Full StackDeveloper

Full Stack Web Developer and leader with greater than ten years of experience in business. Highly developed skills in working effectively with a wide range of abilities and cultures. Ability to extrapolate and solve problems resulting in high performance outcomes. Fast learner with an inquisitive, positive nature and a sense of humor while espousing career as a way of life. Earned a Bachelor's of science in Kinesiology from the University of Illinois at Chicago.

### **Technical Skills**

JavaScript, Python, CSS, Vue/Vuex/Vuetify, React, Express, Pug, Flask, VS Code, GitHub, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose, Node.js, JQuery, RESTful APIs, Bootstrap

### **Projects**

### New Game Plus Website • newgameplus.live

(11/2020 - 2/2021)

- An internship to put my newly developed skills to the test
- Built dynamic company website at: www.newgameplus.live
- Built dynamic dashboard to display traffic analytics to, from and within the program for private company use. Data pulled with RESTful API's and displayed with chartjs.
- Technologies: JavaScript, Vue/Vuex/Vuetify, Sass, Firebase, Postmarkapp, Moment, Chartjs, and multiple RESTful API calls

## **Expense Tracker 5000** • levickane.github.io/expensetracker/

https://github.com/levickane/expensetracker

(April 2021)

- A custom project built during the first month of the coding Bootcamp
- Build a dynamic webpage to track finances using Local Storage and API calls
- Technologies: JavaScript/JQuery, HTML, CSS, Fetch API, Materialize, Local Storage

# **Experience**

### New Game Plus, Chicago, IL

(11/2020 - 2/2021)

Full Stack Developer

- An understanding of the fundamentals of JavaScript, C#, Python, SQL, HTML, and CSS
- Built dynamic company website using Vue/Vuex www.newgameplus.live
- Built dynamic dashboard with Vue/Vuex/Vuetify/Firebase/Firestore to display traffic analytics to, from and within the program. Data pulled from multiple API's. Displayed on chart.js.

# One Legged Levi LLC, Chicago, IL

(2016-2020)

# **Personal Trainer/Entrepreneur**

Client abilities ranged from novice exercisers to professional athletes

- Short and long term paying clients totalling over 200
- Achieved ambitious 15 year business goals within 3 years
- Objectives accomplished by working weekdays only
- Maintained and Optimised SEO for Business Website
- Proficient in Microsoft Office

## LKane Properties, Chicago, IL

(2018-Present)

Property Management, Wealth Portfolio Planning

- 0% vacancy rate across 7 units in 2 buildings
- Tenant feedback: Quick response times, easy to work with, effective problem solver
- Up-to-date knowledge of rental, housing, and mortgage markets
- Maintenance of profit and loss sheet, and projections
- Proficient in Microsoft Office

# **Accomplishments**

## Dare2Tri Paratriathlon Club, Chicago, IL

(2012-2016)

Elite Athlete

- 1st place 2015 National Championship
- 2nd Place 2015 ITU World Championship
- 3rd Place 2015 ITU Continental Championship
- First ever in the world, Single Leg Amputee, to run a sub 20 minute 5K race (2015)
- Maintained personal Website
- Regular public speaking in front of large audiences and company stakeholders

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Certificates:**

Bootcamp Certificate: Northwestern University, Chicago, IL

 A 12-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in Computer Science applied to JavaScript, Browser Based Technologies, API Interaction, Python, Deployment and Command-Line Fundamentals, Databases, Quality Assurance, and Server Side Development encompassing the MERN Stack,

### Python Development: Team Treehouse, teamtreehouse.com

 A self paced, online course built to teach new developers how to write code in Python through the Python Web Development Track. Courses covering the basics of Python and SQL as well as more advanced web applications using the Flask Framework.

# **Schools:**

University of Illinois at Chicago: Chicago, IL

Bachelor of Science in Kinesiology, December 2016